const data = [
  {
    question: 'Question 0',
    options: [
      'Question 0 Option 0',
      'Question 0 Option 1',
      'Question 0 Option 2',
      'Question 0 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 0 Option 0',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 1',
    options: [
      'Question 1 Option 0',
      'Question 1 Option 1',
      'Question 1 Option 2',
      'Question 1 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 1 Option 1',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 2',
    options: [
      'Question 2 Option 0',
      'Question 2 Option 1',
      'Question 2 Option 2',
      'Question 2 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 2 Option 2',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 3',
    options: [
      'Question 3 Option 0',
      'Question 3 Option 1',
      'Question 3 Option 2',
      'Question 3 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 3 Option 3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 4',
    options: [
      'Question 4 Option 0',
      'Question 4 Option 1',
      'Question 4 Option 2',
      'Question 4 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 4 Option 0',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 5',
    options: [
      'Question 5 Option 0',
      'Question 5 Option 1',
      'Question 5 Option 2',
      'Question 5 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 5 Option 1',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 6',
    options: [
      'Question 6 Option 0',
      'Question 6 Option 1',
      'Question 6 Option 2',
      'Question 6 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 6 Option 2',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 7',
    options: [
      'Question 7 Option 0',
      'Question 7 Option 1',
      'Question 7 Option 2',
      'Question 7 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 7 Option 3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 8',
    options: [
      'Question 8 Option 0',
      'Question 8 Option 1',
      'Question 8 Option 2',
      'Question 8 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 8 Option 0',
  },
  {
    question: 'Question 9',
    options: [
      'Question 9 Option 0',
      'Question 9 Option 1',
      'Question 9 Option 2',
      'Question 9 Option 3',
    ],
    answer: 'Question 9 Option 1',
  },
];

export default data;
